cyberlink.com 2018-08-24

# Privacy Policy and Cookies ∣ CyberLink

**Last Update: April 2018**

When you use our services, you trust us with your information. This Privacy Policy is intended to help you understand your right to privacy. 

Our Privacy Policy explains: 

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access, update and manage your information.

We tried to keep this policy as simple, clear and easy to comprehend as possible. You should read this policy carefully in order to protect your right to privacy. You can always manage your [CyberLink membership account](https://membership.cyberlink.com/prog/member/service/update-profile.do?lang=ENU) anytime here.

Personal information on the websites, including without limitation Cyberlink.com, DirectorZone, ImageChef and MoovieLive ("Website"), various CyberLink's mobile apps ("Mobile App") and various CyberLink's computer software products ("Computer Software") products made by CyberLink is collected by CyberLink Corporation. CyberLink's address is 15F, 100, Minquan Road, Xindian District, New Taipei City, Taiwan, R.O.C. and our telephone number is +886-2-8667-1298. Information collected through the Website, Mobile Apps or Computer Software products made by CyberLink may be stored, transferred and processed by CyberLink.com Corp. in the United States, CyberLink Corp. in Taiwan, CyberLink Inc. in Japan and CyberLink Europe B.V. in Netherlands. All transfers will occur in compliance with data transfer requirements of applicable laws and regulations.

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which ads you’ll find most useful to you. We collect information in the following ways: 

  * Information you give us  
As a website visitor, you can browse information exposed on our website without providing any personal information. If you engage in our events, download the trial version of our software or applications, register to become our website member, purchase our products or proceed any other activities related to CyberLink, you will be asked for your personal information. You have choices about the data we collect. When you are asked to provide personal information, which are optional, if you choose not to provide information that is necessary, you may not be able to continue the certain activity.  
The information we collect can include the following: 
    * **Name and contact data**. We collect your first name, last name, display name, email address, postal address, phone number, and/or other similar contact information.
    * **Demographic information.** We collect information about you such as your date of birth, country/region, and/or preferred language.
    * **Comments and posts on online community forums, social media sites, blogs, mobile application platforms, online shopping platforms, and/or online software download sites.** We collect information on your comments, reviews, posts, feedback, surveys and interactions with other forum members you create, made or share in forums.
    * **Information for customer service purposes.** We collect information on your comments, posts, feedback, editorial works, multimedia files, surveys, device information, unique customer ID and interactions with us.
    * **Purchase/Payment data.** When you make purchases, we will collect your payment/purchase information and product/order information when it is necessary.
We may hold and associate any information you provide us with information gathered from other sources, including the social accounts that you choose to associate with your use of the services. Once you are registered at our website, you can view, edit, or delete your account information here after signing into your account. 
  * Information we automatically collect  
When you use our services, we automatically collect some information. We may collect information about your usage of and activity on our services. When you visit our websites, information we may automatically log includes, for example, your operating system, cookies, Internet protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language and the website that you visited before visiting our website.  
This information includes: 
    * **Device information.** We collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information). CyberLink may associate your device identifiers with your CyberLink Account.
    * **Log information.** When you use our services provided by CyberLink, we automatically collect and store certain information in servers. Information we collects includes: 
      * Internet protocol (IP) address.
      * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, language, the date and time of your visit to our Website, Mobile App and/or Computer Software.
      * cookies that may uniquely identify your device or your CyberLink Account.
    * **Location information.** When you use the service on our Website, Mobile App and/or Computer Software, we may collect and process information about your location, via various technologies including Internet protocol (IP) address which indicates a number assigned to every device connected to the Internet assigned in geographic blocks and other identifiers that may, for example, provide CyberLink with information on nearby devices, Wi-Fi access points.
    * **Cookies and similar technologies.** Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a web browser. CyberLink uses cookies and similar technologies, for example, web beacons, to provide our websites and online services and to help collect data. Web beacons are electronic images we may use on our websites or in our emails to deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness, such as whether you open and act on an email that we send you.
Please be informed that any information we collect from your input, feedback, information about you or information obtained from your parents will be treated as personal information. 

CyberLink processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live. We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

We may use your information when using our website for the following purposes: 

  * create and manage your CyberLink Member account, when you purchase from our store, subscribe to our newsletter or download trial software; 
  * create your CyberLink account, when needed to communicate with you;
  * verify your identity and entitlement to certain products or services; 
  * process your purchase transactions; 
  * update you on the status of your order; 
  * allow you to register for products or services you purchase on our Website;
  * manage your subscription plan; 
  * communicate with you should you require technical or customer support service; 
  * subscribe you to newsletter, product updates and upgrades; 
  * connect to you about and manage your participation in contests, offers or promotions; 
  * get your feedback on the trial software;
  * research, implement product improvements and archive purposes; 
  * target advertisement purposes;
  * evaluate and improve quality of our products, services and websites; 
  * provide you with a customized experience when you use our service or visit our website;
  * use your Internet protocol (IP) address to collect anonymous, aggregate statistics: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our service, to help identify you and your activities on the Website (such as registering for an account, uploading/downloading video effects or templates, voting other members’ effects, connecting with other members, forming groups, participating in forum discussions, and purchasing products and services) to gather broad demographic information to analyze traffic to this service in order to understand our visitors’ needs, providing interesting data to our web visitors and to continually improve our Website for them;
  * marketing purposes;
  * promotional collaboration with business partners; and
  * to assist you in finding and communicating with your friends when you use your Facebook account to login into our Website*.

*By using your Facebook login information to log into the Website, Mobile Apps or Computer Software you also permit the Website to access your Facebook information, such as your profile information and privacy settings. Your user profile information including members' pictures and user names, where applicable, are displayed on the Website and Mobile App in order to facilitate user interaction in the social network community. Email addresses are used to send notifications related to the Website and its associated services without disclosing their email addresses. Your full name will never directly reveal to other members unless it is chosen as their profile name/ avatar.

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of CyberLink unless one of the following circumstances applies:

  * For external processing and customer/technical support  
We provide personal information to our affiliates or partners to process on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures or provide necessary customer and technical support in response to customer’s feedback. 
  * For legal reasons  
We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of CyberLink if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:  

    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of CyberLink, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

CyberLink is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities. The Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age, and by the Website’s terms of service, users affirm that they are at least 16 years old. We do not knowingly collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not knowingly distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not knowingly give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without parental consent. We do not entice children with children-targeted games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.

We are committed to protecting your interest when using our services from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

  * We encrypt many of our services using, for example,TLS, SHA256, etc.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
  * We restrict access to personal information to CyberLink’s employees, contractors and agents on a need to know basis in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or websites that may be displayed to you when using our Service. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

If CyberLink is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).

The following notices explain specific privacy practices with respect to certain CyberLink products and services that you may use:

As a visitor to our Website, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. However if you choose to engage in other activities like subscribing to the newsletter or downloading trial software applications, CyberLink may ask you to register to the CyberLink membership program. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities.

  * Your information we collect  
In any event that you choose to provide us with the information when using our website, we will collect your personal information as below in order to help us manage our relationship with you. 
    * Contact details like first and last name, email address, gender, country and preferred language;
    * Shipping and billing information including credit card and payment information (if you intend to purchase any products from our Website)； 
    * Your transaction and browsing history; 
    * Information you submitted to us in order to receive technical assistance or during customer service interactions; 
    * Information about your computer or device, including browser type and settings, IP address, cookies and traffic data relating to your internet connection; 
    * CyberLink product performance data and information about how you use our products and services.

  * Use of your information  
We may use your information when using our website for the following purposes： 
    * create and manage your CyberLink Member account, when you purchase from our store, subscribe to our newsletter or download trial software; 
    * create your CyberLink account, when needed to communicate with you;
    * verify your identity and entitlement to certain products or services; 
    * process your purchase transactions; 
    * update you on the status of your order; 
    * allow you to register for products or services you purchase on our Website;
    * manage your subscription plan; 
    * communicate with you should you require technical or customer support service; 
    * subscribe you to newsletter, product updates and upgrades; 
    * connect to you about and manage your participation in contests, offers or promotions; 
    * get your feedback on the trial software;
    * research, implement product improvements and archive purposes; 
    * target advertisement purposes;
    * evaluate and improve quality of our products, services and websites; 
    * provide you with a customized experience when you use our service or visit our website;
    * use your Internet protocol (IP) address to collect anonymous, aggregate statistics: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our service, to help identify you and your activities on the Website (such as registering for an account, uploading/downloading video effects or templates, voting other members’ effects, connecting with other members, forming groups, participating in forum discussions, and purchasing products and services) to gather broad demographic information to analyze traffic to this service in order to understand our visitors’ needs, providing interesting data to our web visitors and to continually improve our Website for them;
    * marketing purposes; 
    * promotional collaboration with business partners; and
    * to assist you in finding and communicating with your friends when you use your Facebook account to login into our Website*.

*By using your Facebook login information to log into the Website, you also permit the Website to access your Facebook information, such as your profile information and privacy settings. Your user profile information including members' pictures and user names, where applicable, are displayed on the Website and Mobile App in order to facilitate user interaction in the social network community. Email addresses are used to send notifications related to the Website and its associated services without disclosing their email addresses. Your full name will never directly reveal to other members unless it is chosen as their profile name/ avatar. 

  * Cookies  
We use cookies for several purposes, including: 
    * **Sign-in and Authentication.** When you sign into our website using your personal CyberLink account, we store a unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your device. This cookie allows you to move from page to page within the Website without having to sign in again on each page. You can also save your sign-in information so you do not have to sign in again.
    * **Customized experience.** Provide you with a customized experience when you use our service or visit our website
    * **Analytics.** In order to improve your experiences using our websites and services, we use cookies and other identifiers to gather usage and performance data. We use cookies to see which areas of our websites and which features are popular and to count visits to our websites.
    * **Showing Advertising.** We use cookies to record how many visitors have clicked on an advertisement and to record which advertisements you have seen so you don’t see the same one repeatedly.

  * Control of cookies  

    * You may set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it’s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, we may not remember your language preferences.
    * You may also control cooking setting by following the steps below:  

      * Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but provide controls that allow you to turn off, block or delete them. For example, in Google Chrome, you can disable the Websites to save and read cookie data by clicking [Settings] > [Advanced] > [Content Settings] > [Cookies]. For settings of cookies in other browsers may be available in each browser's privacy or help documentation.
      * Please be aware that if you choose to delete cookies, settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, they will be deleted and may need to be recreated.
  * Accessing and updating your personal information  
We want you to be clear about what information we collect and store your information for as long as your account is in use, active or for legitimate purpose in line with our business. We do our best to give you ways to manage your information. You may either: 
    * control who you share information with through our service; 
    * change your Profile name and Profile photo appear in shared endorsements that appear in ads by writing to us or adjust setting in your device or membership account; or 
    * email us at [privacy@cyberlink.com](mailto:privacy@cyberlink.com) Contact Webmaster.
  * More information we collect for cyberlink’s social site. (directorzone.cyberlink.com, moovielive.com, imagechef.com)  
We collect personal interests, self-description uploading/downloading video effects, templates, photos or other materials, voting other members’ effects, connecting/following with other members, messaging with other members, forming groups, participating in forum discussions, and purchasing products and services, movie collections, ratings, DVD region, movie interests and movies watched via PowerDVD to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website, to help identify you and your activities on the Website , to gather broad demographic information to analyze traffic to this Website in order to understand our visitors’ needs, providing interesting data to our web visitors and to continually improve our Website for them.

User profile information including members' pictures and user names are displayed on the Website in order to facilitate user interaction in the CyberLink social websites. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join CyberLink social websites, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the services. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate with each other through the CyberLink social websites services, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. 

  * Disclose of your information when using our website  

    * **When purchasing at our Website**  
The CyberLink website acts as a gateway for you to purchase our products online. Purchases of CyberLink products that are initiated from the CyberLink website are actually completed on the [asknet AG secure website](https://www.asknet.com/), [cleverbridge secure website](https://www.cleverbridge.com/corporate/) or any other shopping cart vendors (collectively known as “Shopping Cart Vendors”). In order to complete a purchase transaction, Shopping Cart Vendors must collect personal information from you, including your credit card number. If you are interested in purchasing CyberLink software through the Shopping Cart Vendors Website, please view the [Privacy Statement of asknet AG](https://shop.cyberlink.com/cgi-bin/pages/privacy_policy/ml=EN) and [Privacy Policy of cleverbridge](https://www.cleverbridge.com/corporate/privacy-policy/). You can be certain that online purchases made through the Shopping Cart Vendors Website are secure. Numerous other online retailers also sell CyberLink products. However, CyberLink does not directly guarantee the privacy of your personal information when making purchases from other Websites. Please consult the Privacy Policy statements posted on those websites directly. 
    * **Third Party Advertisers /Interest-Based Ads**  
CyberLink allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks like Google, to display and/or serve advertisements within the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser the advertisements and links that appear on the website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, or JavaScript) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the content you see. However, please note that if an advertiser requires CyberLink to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 28 - 40) or audience segment (for example, women in California who viewed certain content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Website, Mobile App and Computer Software, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. The information will be recorded and anonymized by the Third Party Advertisers by means of a series of non-reversible encoding functions. Where we provide you with interest-based ads on a website other than our own, we do not track your other activities on that website, if you click on our ads, we will know only the domain you came from. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt out, once you have opted in, of certain practices.   
CyberLink's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control.  
If you do not want us to use your Information in this way, you can simply choose not to give your permission on the websites which we collect your information. Please note that in some regions this may involve un-checking a box. You can also exercise this right at any time by unsubscribing the same.   
We implement Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), to support Google features such as Display Advertising, Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online, Google uses cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Website, and also to report how our ad impressions, uses of ad services are related to your visits to our Website. Google may show our ads on websites across the internet you use. You can also opt-out from being tracked by the foregoing mentioned Google features for the future by following the instructions shown in the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en> the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.  
If you do not wish to receive any of the interest-based ads or do not want to have your personal data provided to third party advertisers, you may change the settings of in the ad network service.  
The website serves the Ads using Google AdSense at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

When using CyberLink’s Mobile App to view our products, we may collect certain information when you access through our Mobile Apps.

  * Your information we collect  

    * Analytic
    * Engaging advertising
    * Crash Reporting
    * Feedback and suggestions
    * Use of CyberLink's service
  * How we use the information on cyberlink’s mobile apps  

    * **Analytic**  
Our apps include app analytic mechanism to log your usage behavior so as to enhance our apps user experiences. The analytics mechanism includes information relating to your usage behavior such as how you use and how often you use our apps. For instances like file types (eg: photo or video), filenames, file extensions, local path of the files that you input to the apps. This analytics do not show information of any photo, video or any materials that you input to the apps.  
Collected information or data are aggregated for analyze, we cannot use the collected data to target a specific person/user. The analytics are collect via vendors name below: 
      * Flurry;
      * Google Firebase Analytics (here’s our partner’s privacy [statement](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)); and
      * Facebook Analytics (here’s our partner’s privacy [statement](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation))
    * **Engaging advertising**  
CyberLink allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks to display and/or serve advertisements within the Mobile apps. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your mobile app the advertisements and links that appear on mobile app. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, or JavaScript) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the content you see.  
Our Mobile App advertising vendor as below:  

      * Facebook Audience Network (here’s our partner’s privacy [statement](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation))
      * Google Admob (here’s our partner’s privacy [statement](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/))
      * Intowow Innovation
    * **Crash Reporting**  
Our apps use Fabrics or Google Play services to collect crash logs when the apps running on your devices crashed or stopped responding.
    * **Feedback and suggestions**  
Your input and screenshots provided in “Feedback” / Report an Issue” pages in the apps.
    * **Use of CyberLink's service**  
When you use CyberLink Cloud, DirectorZone, MoovieLive, ImageChef, we may collect your usage behavior so as to enhance our apps user experiences.
  * Disclose of your information when using our mobile apps  

    * **When purchasing at our Mobile App**  
Our Mobile App acts as a gateway for you to purchase our products online. Purchases of CyberLink products that are initiated from our Mobile App are actually completed on Apple App Store, Google Play, Microsoft Store or any other mobile application stores (collectively known as “Mobile App Stores”). In order to complete a purchase transaction, Mobile App Stores must collect personal information from you, including your credit card number. If you are interested in purchasing CyberLink software through the Mobile App Stores, please view the Privacy Statement of respective stores. 

We also provide our service via our Computer Software (Windows, Mac applications) which are installed on your computers.

  * Your information we collect  
In any event that you choose to provide us with the information when using our Computer Software, we will use Unique User ID (UUID) to uniquely identify your device. This UUID is generated by combining Windows Security ID (SID) on your computer, and a randomly generated large number so as to enable us to identify this computer which has been identified to have installed our Computer Software. You may reset this UUID on your device by closing all CyberLink products on your computer and remove this registry key at “Computer\HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\CyberLink\CBE” using Windows Registry Editor.” 
  * Use of your information  
We may use your information when using our Computer Software for the following purposes：  

    * **CyberLink Product Improvement Program (CPIP):**  
Collecting and analyzing how our applications are being used helps improve our product design, feature development and bug fixings. The CPIP program collects the way you use features in CyberLink applications, your search input, filenames, file extension names of the files that you input to CyberLink applications. It also includes software application information or device information which doesn’t include personal info such as Software release number, Product Key, UI language, OS version, device vendor, device model name, vendor and model name for specific hardware component (like CPU, GPU), the name of your device. To opt-out CPIP, you can go to settings of each CyberLink application to and uncheck the “I want to participate” in CPIP section. 
    * **Product Info Notice (Customized Ads / Patch / Content Pack Information)**  
To receive latest software patch info or sales offers in CyberLink applications, includes software application information or device information which doesn’t include personal info such as Software release number, Product Key, UI language, OS version, device vendor name. If users opted in to CPIP, then data collected in CPIP would be linked to Customized Ads / Patch / Content Pack to provide more interesting info for users. To opt-out latest product info notice, you can go to settings of each CyberLink application and disable the “Check for product update information”, or “Automatically check for software updates” option 
    * **Error Reporting**  
Error Reporting helps CyberLink to build more robust product by fixing product crash issues. When product crashed, an Error Reporting dialog pops up, debug information will be sent back only when users consent to send them back to CyberLink. The Error Reporting collects only program data and memory dump which does not intended to collect any personal info. If email is provided by the users, users affirm that they agrees that CyberLink may contact users for more information to help CyberLink fix the program crash issues. 
    * **Product Registration**  
When users opt-in to register CyberLink products that they use or purchase, they can find the Product Registration dialog. The dialog may popup during they use the product or can be find in the product About dialogs. When user provided their email, their email will be used to register a CyberLink Account with a randomly generated secured password. Users can reset their password in this website and later access their registered product keys in the member zone of this website. Upon the registration, email address, birthday (if user opt-in to provide) from the user will be collected along with the UUID (mentioned above) and other info that are not unique to this user including: software release number, Product Key, UI language, OS version, device vendor, device model name, vendor and model name for specific hardware component (like CPU, GPU), the name of users’ device. 
    * **Codec activation**  
When you use certain technologies essential to multi-media functions for the first time, the software application will collect the serial number of your computer system and the product key (CD key) for activation purposes only. This data collection takes place only once for each codec features, it won’t collect how often or how many time you use each codec. 
    * **Use of CyberLink’s service**  
When you use CyberLink service in the Computer Software such as CyberLink Cloud, DirectorZone, MoovieLive, ImageChef. We may collect your usage behavior so as to enhance our Computer Software user experiences, you may want to refer to the WEBSITE section of this Privacy Policy. 
  * Disclose of your information when using our computer software  

    * **When purchasing at our computer software**  
Our Computer Software acts as a gateway for you to purchase our products online. Purchases of CyberLink products that are initiated from our Computer Software would be directed to our Website, you may want to refer to the DISCLOSE OF YOUR INFORMATION WHEN USING OUR WEBSITE section of this Privacy Policy to understand how we manage your information with our Shopping Cart Vendors.
